Guide to the William Manchester Papers, 1934 - 2004
William Manchester Papers1934 - 2004
- Series I: Writings, 1943-1995
  - Books
    - The Death of a President
      - Research
        - Documents
          - 23. Parkland Hospital
            - Document #175, Photograph of trauma room number 1, undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
            - Document #176, Names and titles of physicians who attended JFK and Connally, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
            - Document #177, Additional emergency room staff, 1963 Nov 26 (Box 49, Folder 18)
            - Document #178, Patients admitted for treatment between 12:38 p.m. and 2:19 p.m., undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
            - Document #179, Patients undergoing treatment at the time the President was brought in, undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
            - Document #180, Oswald attendents, undated (Box 49, Folder 21)
            - Document #181, Anne Ferguson report, undated (Box 49, Folder 22)
            - Document #182, Jack Price memo, 1963 Nov 27 (Box 49, Folder 23)
            - Document #183, Tom Shires memo, undated (Box 49, Folder 24)
            - Document #184, Phyllis Bartlett memo, undated (Box 49, Folder 25)
            - Document #185, Activities of David Sanders, undated (Box 49, Folder 26)
            - Document #186, Activities of Rosa Majors, undated (Box 49, Folder 27)
            - Document #187, Activities of Shirley Randall, undated (Box 49, Folder 28)
            - Document #188, Activities of Bertha Lozano, undated (Box 49, Folder 29)
            - Document #189, Activities of Maragaret Hinchcliffe, undated (Box 49, Folder 30)
            - Document #190, Activities of Era Lumpkin, undated (Box 49, Folder 31)
            - Document #191, Diana Brown to Elizabeth Wright, undated (Box 49, Folder 32)
            - Document #192, C.J. Price memo, 1963 Dec 11 (Box 49, Folder 33)
            - Document #193, Peter Geilich memo, 1963 Nov 26 (Box 49, Folder 34)
            - Document #194, Steven Landregan memo, undated (Box 49, Folder 35)
            - Document #195, R.G. Holcomb memo, undated (Box 49, Folder 36)
            - Document #196, Jack Price memo, undated (Box 49, Folder 37)
            - Document #197, Betty B. memo, undated (Box 49, Folder 38)
            - Document #198, Oneal Funeral Directors Yellow Pages advertisement, undated (Box 49, Folder 39)
            - Document #199, Burial-transit permit, JFK, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 49, Folder 40)
            - Document #200, JFK death certificate, 1963 Dec 11 (Box 49, Folder 41)
          - 24. Reaction, and WH Blessing 4:25 A. M.
            - Document #201, Thomas Cain memo, undated (Box 49, Folder 42)
            - Document #202, Application for and ticket to Austin dinner, 11-22-63 (Box 49, Folder 43)
            - Document #203, John Kuhn blessing, 1964 Aug 17 (Box 49, Folder 44)
          - 25. Saturday, 11-23-64
            - Document #204, Orville Freeman notes, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 49, Folder 45)
            - Document #205, Francis Carpenter to WM, 1964 Aug 24 (Box 49, Folder 46)
            - Document #206, Adlai Stevenson statement, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 49, Folder 47)
            - Document #207, Adlai Stevenson statement, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 49, Folder 48)
            - Document #208, Art Buchwald to WM, 1964 Sep 14 (Box 49, Folder 49)
            - Document #209, Byron Skelton to RFK, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 49, Folder 50)
          - 26. Sunday, 11-24-63
            - Document #210, Mass documents, undated (Box 49, Folder 51)
          - 27. General (cont.)
            - Document #211, Orville Freeman memo, 1963 Nov 23-25 (Box 49, Folder 52)
            - Document #212, Chester Clifton bio, undated (Box 49, Folder 53)
            - Document #213, Godfrey McHugh bio, undated (Box 49, Folder 54)
            - Document #214, Tazwell Shepard bio, 1961 Jan 23 (Box 49, Folder 55)
            - Document #215, Sue to WM, 1964 Aug 26 (Box 49, Folder 56)
            - Document #216, Adlai Stevenson statement, 1963 Nov 26 (Box 49, Folder 57)
            - Document #217, John Kenneth Galbraith journal, 1963 Nov 26 (Box 49, Folder 58)
            - Document #218, Hotel bill, 1963 Nov 22-27 (Box 49, Folder 59)
            - Document #219, Charles Spalding to WM, 1964 Sep 28 (Box 49, Folder 60)
            - Document #220, Activities of Doris Nelson, undated (Box 49, Folder 61)
          - Photocopies of documents
            These documents are photocopies of the above numbered documents. In some cases, they fill gaps in the list of numbered documents. Restricted materials have been removed.
            - Document #1, Pamela Turnure to JBK [restricted], 1963 Nov 7 (Box 58)
            - Document #5, Schedule, 1963 Nov 21-22 (Box 49, Folder 62)
            - Document #8, Proposed schedule at LBJ's ranch, undated (Box 49, Folder 63)
            - Document #9, Nancy Tuckerman to JBK [restricted], 1963 Nov 6 (Box 58)
            - Document #10, Nancy Tuckerman to JBK [restricted], 1963 Nov 7 (Box 58)
            - Document #12, JBK to JFK, "Salerno letter" [restricted], undated (Box 58)
            - Document #13, Nancy Tuckerman to JFK [restricted], 1963 Nov 20 (Box 58)
            - Document #15, Rose Kennedy to JBK [restricted], 1963 Nov 20 (Box 58)
            - Document #17, Nancy Tuckerman to JBK [restricted], undated (Box 58)
            - Document #25, Speech draft, JBK and Nancy Turnure, undated (Box 49, Folder 64)
            - Document #29, Pamela Turnure notes for JBK [restricted], undated (Box 58)
            - Document #73, LBJ to Caroline Kennedy, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 49, Folder 65)
            - Document #74, LBJ to John F. Kennedy Jr., 1963 Nov 22 (Box 49, Folder 66)
            - Document #91, Arthur Schlesinger to JBK, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 49, Folder 67)
            - Document #92, Arthur Schlesinger to JBK, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 49, Folder 68)
            - Document #93, RFK to JBK [restricted], 1963 Nov 23 (Box 58)
            - Document #95, JBK notes, [1963 Nov 22-24] (Box 49, Folder 69)
            - Document #96, John Kenneth Galbraith to JBK, [1963 Nov 22] (Box 49, Folder 70)
            - Document #97, JBK to JFK [restricted], 1962 Mar 13 (Box 58)
            - Document #98, Bunny Mellon to JBK, undated (Box 49, Folder 71)
            - Document #99, Mike Manfield statement, 1963 Nov 24 (Box 49, Folder 72)
            - Document #111, Mary Jan Duris to WM, 1964 Apr 21 (Box 49, Folder 73)
            - Document #114, McGeorge Bundy to JBK, 1963 Nov 28 (Box 49, Folder 74)
            - Document #115, McGeorge Bundy to JBK, undated (Box 49, Folder 75)
            - Document #117, JBK to Nikita Krushchev [alternate draft], 1963 Dec 1 (Box 49, Folder 76)
            - Document #119, JBK notes, undated (Box 49, Folder 77)
            - Document #120, E.K. Auerbach to JBK, 1963 Dec 20 (Box 49, Folder 78)
            - Document #121, JBK notes, undated (Box 49, Folder 79)
            - Document #122, LBJ to JBK, 1963 Dec 1 (Box 49, Folder 80)
            - Document #123, LBJ to JBK, 1963 Nov 29 (Box 49, Folder 81)
            - Document #124, JBK to LBJ, 1963 Dec 1 (Box 49, Folder 82)
            - Document #125, Lady Bird Johnson to JBK, 1963 Dec 5 (Box 49, Folder 83)
            - Document #136, Jean Kennedy Smith notes, 1963 Nov 22-28 (Box 49, Folder 84)
            - Document #154, JFK letters, 1963 Nov 20 (Box 49, Folder 85)
          - Additional documents
            - Prince Andrew, regarding the death of, undated (Box 49, Folder 86)
            - Bird, Sam, to WM, 1968 Jan 3 (Box 49, Folder 87)
            - Cuesta, Lourdes, to WM, 1965 May 6 (Box 49, Folder 88)
            - Elsbree, Hugh, Library of Congress, undated (Box 49, Folder 89)
            - Gonzales, Henry, to WM, 1965 May 7 (Box 49, Folder 90)
            - Kahn, Julius, to WM, 1965 Mar 18 (Box 49, Folder 91)
            - JFK grave site postcard, undated (Box 49, Folder 92)
            - Lehrer, Jim, to WM, 1965 Jan 20 (Box 49, Folder 93)
            - Lehrer, Jim, to WM, 1966 Mar 1 (Box 49, Folder 94)
            - Lehrer, Jim, to WM, 1966 May 25 (Box 49, Folder 95)
            - McGrory, Mary, In Memorian: John Fitzgerald Kennedy, 1963 Nov (Box 49, Folder 96)
            - McNally, George, White House Communications Agency Signal Operations instructions voice call signs, 1963 Jan 1 (Box 49, Folder 97)
            - Military District of Washington, D.C., press release, 1963 Nov 25 (Box 49, Folder 98)
            - Monday's child is fair of face, undated (Box 49, Folder 99)
            - National Enquirer, 1964 Aug 30 (Box 49, Folder 100)
            - O'Donnell, Kenneth, Texas folder, 1963 Nov (Box 50, Folder 1)
            - Orlady, Harry, to WM, 1966 Mar 2 (Box 50, Folder 2)
            - Price, C.J., to WM, 1965 Feb 24 (Box 50, Folder 3)
            - Schlesinger, Arthur, to WM, 1965 Jul 6 (Box 50, Folder 4)
            - Sorensen, Theodore, to WM, 1966 Mar 7 (Box 50, Folder 5)
            - Sorensen, Theodore, Epilogue, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
            - Taylor, Telford, to WM, 1967 Jan 6 (Box 50, Folder 7)
            - Thompson, James, to WM, 1964 Dec 6 (Box 50, Folder 8)
            - Valenti, Jack, to WM [contains LBJ's responses to WM's questions], 1965 Jun 24 (Box 50, Folder 9)
            - Valenti, Jack, to WM, 1965 Jul 13 (Box 50, Folder 10)
            - Warner, Jack, and Burrell Peterson, 1965 Feb 5 (Box 50, Folder 11)
            - Wells, Tom, to WM, 1964 Dec 18 (Box 50, Folder 12)
            - Yarborough: Portrait of a People's Senator, undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
            - Unidentified, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
          - Misc. documents
            - Hohne, Hansjoachim, to WM, 1968 Mar 28 (Box 50, Folder 15)
            - Humphrey, Hubert, memorandum, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 50, Folder 16)
            - Kellerman, note re:, undated (Box 50, Folder 17)
            - JBK to WM, [1964?] (Box 50, Folder 18)
            - JFK phone calls, 1964 Nov 19-22 (Box 50, Folder 19)
            - JFK to Ralph Yarborough, [1950s] (Box 50, Folder 20)
            - John F. Kennedy Center for Special Warfare, Office of Information, The Green Beret, undated (Box 50, Folder 21)
            - Metzler, John, to WM, 1966 Jan 28 (Box 50, Folder 22)
            - Photocopies WM requested
              - --, Grace to WM, 1967 Mar 31 (Box 50, Folder 23)
              - Lincoln, Evelyn, notes, undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
              - Itinerary, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 50, Folder 25)
              - LBJ to Caroline Kennedy, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 50, Folder 26)
              - LBJ to JBK, 1963 Dec 1 (Box 50, Folder 27)
              - LBJ to John F. Kennedy Jr., 1963 Nov 22 (Box 50, Folder 28)
              - Joint Chiefs of Staff flash, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 50, Folder 29)
              - Josephy, Alvin, to WM, 1965 Jun 21 (Box 50, Folder 30)
              - JBK to Nikita Krushchev, 1963 Dec 1 (Box 50, Folder 31)
              - JBK notes, [1963 Nov] (Box 50, Folder 32)
              - JBK speech draft, [1963 Nov] (Box 50, Folder 33)
              - Registration of patients, Parkland Memorial Hospital, 1963 Nov 22 (Box 50, Folder 34)
              - Swindal, James, to WM, undated (Box 50, Folder 35)
            - Readings for graveside--Kennedy speeches, undated (Box 50, Folder 36)
            - Shriver, Eunice, to WM, 1965 Aug 25 (Box 50, Folder 37)
            - Sidey Hugh, to WM, 1966 Oct 4 (Box 50, Folder 38)
            - Sorensen, Theodore, to WM, 1965 May 17 (Box 50, Folder 39)
            - Tallmadge, M., to JBK, 1963 Nov 11 (Box 50, Folder 40)
            - Thomas, Evan, to WM, 1966 Sep 16 (Box 50, Folder 41)
            - Unidentified, undated (Box 50, Folder 42)
          - Newsweek, 1963 Dec 2 (Box 50, Folder 43)
          - National Geographic, 1964 Mar (Box 50, Folder 44)
          - U.S. News and World Report, 1963 Dec 2 (Box 50, Folder 45)
          - Time, 1963 Nov 29 (Box 50, Folder 46)
          - Life, JFK memorial edition (Box 50, Folder 47)
          - Newsweek, 1963 Dec 9 (Box 50, Folder 48)
          - Time, 1963 Dec 6 (Box 50, Folder 49)
          - AP bulletins and notes, 1963 Nov 22-25 (Box 50, Folder 50)
          - Carpenter, Elizabeth, 1965 Jun 7 (Box 50, Folder 51)
          - Childe Harold (Box 50, Folder 52)
          - Ecclesiastes 12 (Box 50, Folder 53)
          - WM notes: examination of basement coffin, 1964 Nov 9 (Box 50, Folder 54)
          - WM notes: length of corridor, Bethesda Naval Hospital, [1964] Apr 12 (Box 50, Folder 55)
          - Parkland Memorial Hospital statements
            - Bell, Audrey, 1963 Nov 25 (Box 50, Folder 56)
            - [Duetin?], Bob, undated (Box 50, Folder 57)
            - Dunn, Tommy, undated (Box 50, Folder 58)
            - Gerloff, Charles, 1963 Nov 28 (Box 50, Folder 59)
            - Haywood, Willie, undated (Box 50, Folder 60)
            - Hutton, Patricia, undated (Box 50, Folder 61)
            - Lennon, Sally, undated (Box 50, Folder 62)
            - Lively, Bessie, undated (Box 50, Folder 63)
            - Locklin, Henry, undated (Box 50, Folder 64)
            - Moore, L.G., undated (Box 50, Folder 65)
            - Pomeroy, Jill, undated (Box 50, Folder 66)
            - Price, Charles, 1963 Nov 27 (Box 50, Folder 67)
            - Reddick, Carol, 1963 Dec 2 (Box 50, Folder 68)
            - Richards, Joe, undated (Box 50, Folder 69)
            - Scott, Frances, undated (Box 50, Folder 70)
            - Shankles, Joe, 1963 Dec 1 (Box 50, Folder 71)
            - Shelby, Faye, undated (Box 50, Folder 72)
            - Standridge, Jeanette, undated (Box 50, Folder 73)
            - Tarrant, Jean, undated (Box 50, Folder 74)
            - Uzee, Norris, 1963 Dec 5 (Box 50, Folder 75)
            - Watkins, C., undated (Box 50, Folder 76)
            - Wright, O.P., 1963 Dec 4 (Box 50, Folder 77)
            - Wyatt, Odell, undated (Box 50, Folder 78)
          - Warren Commission notes (Box 50, Folder 79)
        - Clipping files
          - List of clipping folders (Box 50, Folder 80)
          - 1. Prologue: Nov. 20 (Box 50, Folder 81)
          - 2. Nov. 21 (Thurs.) (Box 50, Folder 82)
          - 3. Nov. 22-General (Fri.) (Box 50, Folder 83)
          - 4. Nov. 22-to Motorcade (Box 50, Folder 84)
          - 5. Nov. 22 Motorcade to 1 P.M. (Box 50, Folder 85)
          - 6. Nov. 22 1 PM to takeoff (Fri.) (Box 50, Folder 86)
          - 12. Nov. 23 (Sat.) (Box 50, Folder 87)
          - 13. Reaction-U.S. (Box 50, Folder 88-89)
          - 14. Reaction abroad (Box 51, Folder 1)
          - 15. Mourning-U.S. (Box 51, Folder 2)
          - 16. Mourning abroad (Box 51, Folder 3)
          - 18. Nov. 24 (Sun.) (Box 51, Folder 4)
          - 19. Night of Nov. 24-25 [original folder empty] (Box 51, Folder 5)
          - 24. Nov. 25-Reception [original folder empty] (Box 51, Folder 6)
          - 25. Nov. 25 (Mon.)-General (Box 51, Folder 7)
          - 27. Aftermath: JBK and family of JFK (Box 51, Folder 8)
          - 28. Oswald: Background and General (Box 51, Folder 9)
          - 29. Oswald, Nov. 22 (Box 51, Folder 10)
          - 30. Oswald Nov. 24 (Sun.) (Box 51, Folder 11)
          - 33. Ruby, background (Box 51, Folder 12)
          - 36. Ruby: Aftermath (Box 51, Folder 13)
          - 37. LBJ (Box 51, Folder 14)
          - 38. Aftermath: General (Box 51, Folder 15)
          - 39. Misc.-clips (Box 51, Folder 16)
          - 40. Dallas (Box 51, Folder 17)
          - 41. Questions (Box 51, Folder 18-21)
          - 41. Questions [Manchester] (Box 51, Folder 22-24)
            Contains lists of questions posed by WM.
          - Epilogue-General (Box 51, Folder 25-27)
            - Connally (Box 51, Folder 28)
            - FBI-Warren probes (Box 51, Folder 29)
            - Guns (Box 51, Folder 30)
            - Immediate recovery (Box 51, Folder 31)
            - Kennedy Library (Box 51, Folder 32)
            - LBJ's Washington (Box 51, Folder 33)
            - Legend (Box 51, Folder 34)
            - Marina, Marga, Mrs. Tippit (Box 51, Folder 35)
            - Protection-SS and FBI (Box 51, Folder 36)
            - Renaming places (Box 51, Folder 37)
            - Ruby (Box 51, Folder 38)
          - General (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Cape Cod (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Clippings (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - Codes (Box 52, Folder 4-5)
        - Codes, JBK and RFK tapes [restricted] (Box 58)
        - Commission [Warren] (Box 52, Folder 6-7)
        - Connally, John, to JBK, [1963 Nov?] (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - Gallagher, Mary, to WM via Joe Giadarno, 1964 Jun 11 (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - Greenstein, F.I., College students' reactions to the assassination, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - Greenstein, F.I., Young men and the death of a young president, 1965 (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - Hotel bill, Life, 1963 Nov 22-26 (Box 52, Folder 12)
        - JBK notes, [1964?] (Box 52, Folder 13-14)
        - JFK Mass cards, 1963 Nov 25 (Box 52, Folder 15)
        - Kirschner, David, The death of a president: reactions of psychoanalytic patients, 1965 Jan (Box 52, Folder 16)
        - Lancer (home safe) (Box 52, Folder 17)
        - Library of Congress, 1963-64 (Box 52, Folder 18)
        - Maps (Box 52, Folder 19-20)
        - Music (Box 52, Folder 21)
        - The New York Times Index, 1963 Nov 16-30 (Box 52, Folder 22)
        - Notes (Box 52, Folder 23-24)
        - Oswald, Maria (Box 52, Folder 25)
        - Parkland Memorial Hospital (Box 52, Folder 26)
        - Parkland Memorial Hospital drawing (Box 52, Folder 27)
        - President's schedule, 1963 Nov 19-21 (Box 52, Folder 28)
        - Roberts to Goldman, 1963 Nov 23 (Box 52, Folder 29)
        - Rothstein, D.A., Presidential assassination syndrome; P.B. Sheatskey and J.J. Feldman, The assassination of President Kennedy (Box 52, Folder 30)
        - St. Matthew's Cathedral (Box 52, Folder 31)
        - Sigel, Roberta, to WM, 1965 Jul 19 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - Sigel, Roberta, Death of a president and school children's reaction to it-An exploration into political socialization (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - Sigel, Roberta, Television in the lives of children during a national crisis-Report on the reactions of school children to the assassination of John F. Kennedy (Box 53, Folder 3)
        - Smith, H. Merle, The Year That Was, 1964 May 18 (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - Sources (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - TDOAP material (Box 53, Folder 6)
        - Texas trip (Box 53, Folder 7-11)
        - Timeline, Nov. 22 (Box 53, Folder 12)
        - Tippit, Mrs. J.D., to JBK, [1963 Nov?] (Box 53, Folder 13)
        - White House Communications Agency, Signal Operation Instructions, Voice Call Signs, 1963 Jan 1 (Box 53, Folder 14)
        - Wolfenstein, Martha, Death of a parent and death of a president: Children's reactions to two kinds of loss, 1964 Apr 3 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Clumps [restricted] (Box 368-373)
      - Drafts [restricted] (Box 61)
        - Outlines, holographs and typescripts, [1965] (Box 61)
        - Preliminary draft, [1965] (Box 61)
          - Prologue, holograph (Box 61)
          - Prologue (1), typescript with author emendations (Box 61)
          - One - Wand (2), typescript with author emendations (Box 61)
          - SS 100 X (3), typescript with author emendations (Box 61)
          - Three - Market (A) (4), typescript with author emendations (Box 61)
          - Market (B) (5), typescript with author emendations (Box 61)
          - Volunteer (A) (7), typescript with author emendations (Box 61)
          - Volunteer (B), typescript with author emendations (Box 61)
          - Volunteer (C), typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
        - Original manuscript draft, completed, 1966 Mar (Box 62)
          - Front matter, typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
          - Prologue, typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
          - Book One, Charcoal, One - Wand, typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
          - Two - SS 100 X, typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
          - Three - Market, typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
          - Four - Volunteer, typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
          - Five - Go, Stranger, typescript with author emendations (Box 62)
          - Book Two, Castle, Six - Angel, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Seven - Lace, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Eight - Crown, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Nine - Passion, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Ten - Lux, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Epilogue + Appendix, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Sources, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Author's interviews (Box 63)
          - Chronology (Box 63)
          - Revisions, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Notes and revisions by Vera to make first clean copy, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - New pages, typescript with author emendations (Box 63)
          - Front matter, etc., typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Prologue, second draft, typescript (Box 64)
          - Wand, second draft, typescript (Box 64)
          - Wand, second draft rev., typescript (Box 64)
          - SS 100 X, typescript (Box 64)
          - Market, typescript (Box 64)
          - Volunteer, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Revisions, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
        - Manuscript delivered to New York, 1966 Mar (Box 64)
          - Front matter and Prologue, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Book One, Charcoal, Chapter 1, Wand, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Chapter 2, SS 100 X, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Chapter 3, Market, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Chapter 4, Volunteer, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Chapter 5, Go, Stranger, typescript with author emendations (Box 64)
          - Book Two, Castle, Chapter 6, Angel, typescript with author emendations (Box 65)
          - Chapter 7, Lace, typescript with author emendations (Box 65)
          - Chapter 8, Crown, typescript with author emendations (Box 65)
          - Chapter 9, Passion, typescript with author emendations (Box 65)
          - Chapter 10, Light, typescript with author emendations (Box 65)
          - Epilogue, Legend, typescript with author emendations (Box 65)
          - Appendices, typescript with author emendations (Box 65)
          - Replaced pages (Box 65)
          - Donald Congdon's copy, [1966 Apr] (Box 65)
            - Front matter and Prologue, typescript (Box 65)
            - Book One, Charcoal, Chapter 1, Wand, typescript (Box 65)
            - Chapter 2, SS 100 X, typescript (Box 66)
            - Chapter 3, Market, typescript (Box 66)
            - Chapter 4, Volunteer, typescript (Box 66)
            - Chapter 5, Go, Stranger, typescript (Box 66)
            - Book Two, Chapter 6, Angel, typescript (Box 66)
            - Chapter 7, Lace, typescript (Box 66)
            - Chapter 8, Crown, typescript (Box 66)
            - Chapter 9, Passion, typescript (Box 67)
            - Chapter 10, Light, typescrpt (Box 67)
            - Epilogue, Legend, typescript (Box 67)
            - Appendices, typescript (Box 67)
          - Revisions, typescript with author's emendations, [1966 May-Jul] (Box 67)
          - Final changes in MSS, typescript with author's emendations, 1966 Jul (Box 67)
        - Corrected carbon, 1966 Jul (Box 67)
          - Foreward, typescript with author's emendations (Box 67)
          - Prologue, typescript with author's emendations (Box 67)
          - Book One, Charcoal, Chapter 1, Wand, typescript with author's emendations (Box 67)
          - Chapter 2, SS 100 X, typescript with author's emendations (Box 67)